PROFILE

Hello there! My name is Domenico Antonio Barberi but you can call me Nico. I am a recent graduate from the Full Stack Web Developer Bootcamp at the University of Toronto. I am experienced with building MERN stack applications but also currently exploring Vue.js (3.X)!

Based in London Ont Canada

CONTACT

PHONE: 1-(226)-224-8292

Portfolio:

https://domenico-barberi-reactportfolio.netlify.app/

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/domenico-a-barberi/

Email:

DomenicoABarberi@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Photography
Custom Mechanical Keyboards
Video Games

DOMENICO BARBERI

EDUCATION:

University Of Toronto (EdX)

December 2022 - June 2023

Full Stack Web Development Coding Bootcamp

Forest Heights Collegiate Institute

September 2009 - June 2013

High School Diploma

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Coco Paving & Delko Paving [Flagger/Traffic Control] [2022-2023]

• Traffic control and flagging for paving crews on highways/suburbs.

Freelance Video Editor

[2020-2022 (Pandemic)]

- Utilized professional video editing software, including Final Cut Pro, Davinci Resolve, and Sony Vegas
- Collaborated with clients to meet their video editing needs

Forever 21 [Cashier/Stock]

[2018-2020]

• Provided excellent customer service, operated cash registers, and handled stock management.

Family Landscaping/Demolition Business

[2016-2017]

- Gained experience in demolition, concrete work, and landscaping.
- Developed skills in project coordination and problem-solving.

Lowe's Home Improvement [Loader/Receiving/Cashier]

- Received training in shipping and receiving as well as operating forklift equipment.
- Maintained accurate inventory records and ensured timely and efficient merchandise handling.